<?xml version="1.0"?>
<rss version="2.0">
   <channel>
      <title>Hugot Blog</title>
      <link>https://hugot.nl/blog.html</link>
      <description>Hugo's personal blog</description>
      <language>en-us</language>
      <pubDate>Mon 17 Feb 2020 11:55:42 AM CET</pubDate>
      <lastBuildDate>Mon 17 Feb 2020 11:55:42 AM CET</lastBuildDate>
      <docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs>
      <generator>Hugo's Custom Bash Script</generator>
      <managingEditor>social@hugot.nl</managingEditor>
      <webMaster>infra@hugot.nl</webMaster>
<item><title> How To Use Your Email Client For Physical Mail </title><link>https://hugot.nl/posts/use-your-mail-client-for-physical-mail/index.html</link><description>Whether it&#39;s to re-read a conversation, find a plane ticket I ordered or check
when a meeting was planned, I often find myself looking up old emails. It&#39;s
usually easy to do so because email clients are designed for the task: Many of
them support full-text search and some even complement that with advanced
tagging and categorization systems. To be honest I have become completely</description><pubDate>Mon 17 Feb 2020 11:55:42 AM CET</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="false"> How To Use Your Email Client For Physical Mail MjYyNjk3NDk5NCA0MDkzCg==</guid>
</item>
<item><title> Creating a Simple Static Blog </title><link>https://hugot.nl/posts/simple-static-blog/index.html</link><description>I love personal websites. It&#39;s amazing that people can share content with the
entire world just by writing some text and throwing it behind a web server. I
wanted to know what that is like, so I set out to create a personal website of
my own. As you can see I succeeded in doing so, but getting here wasn&#39;t as
straight forward as I initially thought it would be. I thought that, being a</description><pubDate>Sat 08 Feb 2020 12:14:16 PM CET</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="false"> Creating a Simple Static Blog Mzg5NDU4OTEwNiA2MTI4Cg==</guid>
</item>
<item><title> Introduction </title><link>https://hugot.nl/posts/introduction/index.html</link><description>Hello, welcome to my blog! My name is Hugo. I am a 22 year old Software
Engineering student from the Netherlands. Software development is a huge part
of my life, I write a lot of (weird) programs to scratch my own itch and most
software I create is open_source by default. I also run a one-man company that
provides some IT services on the side.</description><pubDate>Sat 08 Feb 2020 09:30:06 AM CET</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="false"> Introduction MjM3MzUyOTAwNSA5MDYK</guid>
</item>
</channel>
</rss>
